// data/questions.js

const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Apa ibu kota Indonesia?",
    options: ["Jakarta", "Bali", "Surabaya", "Bandung"],
    correctAnswer: "Jakarta",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Siapa penemu telepon?",
    options: [
      "Thomas Edison",
      "Alexander Graham Bell",
      "Nikola Tesla",
      "Albert Einstein",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Alexander Graham Bell",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Apa hasil dari 3 + 2?",
    options: ["5", "6", "4", "7"],
    correctAnswer: "5",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "Apa ibu kota Indonesia?",
    options: ["Jakarta", "Bali", "Surabaya", "Bandung"],
    correctAnswer: "Jakarta",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Siapa penemu telepon?",
    options: [
      "Thomas Edison",
      "Alexander Graham Bell",
      "Nikola Tesla",
      "Albert Einstein",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Alexander Graham Bell",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Apa hasil dari 3 + 2?",
    options: ["5", "6", "4", "7"],
    correctAnswer: "5",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Apa ibu kota Indonesia?",
    options: ["Jakarta", "Bali", "Surabaya", "Bandung"],
    correctAnswer: "Jakarta",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Siapa penemu telepon?",
    options: [
      "Thomas Edison",
      "Alexander Graham Bell",
      "Nikola Tesla",
      "Albert Einstein",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Alexander Graham Bell",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Apa hasil dari 3 + 2?",
    options: ["5", "6", "4", "7"],
    correctAnswer: "5",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "Apa ibu kota Indonesia?",
    options: ["Jakarta", "Bali", "Surabaya", "Bandung"],
    correctAnswer: "Jakarta",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "Siapa penemu telepon?",
    options: [
      "Thomas Edison",
      "Alexander Graham Bell",
      "Nikola Tesla",
      "Albert Einstein",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Alexander Graham Bell",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Apa hasil dari 3 + 2?",
    options: ["5", "6", "4", "7"],
    correctAnswer: "5",
  },
];

export default questions;
